What... is this?
I feel as if my soul's been flung
somewhere unimaginably far...
Has it truly been a thousand
years since we last assembled?
We have not since the Silver Age.
The one back then was
exceptional, as well.
The one who, at level 255,
tamed all four of us and
returned our powers to us.
How...
I've never heard these voices
before, but I know them.
The day will soon come
when we all come together and
fully regain our powers.
It will be the most auspicious day
since the moment of creation!
My goodness. You seem
quite fond of this boy,
"Mad Dog" Leviathan.
Was I... hearing things?
A voice from the heavens...
That was God's voice, wasn't it?!
I heard it, too!
The heavens have placed their
hopes in the Thirteenth Prince!
Incredible!
I heard it, too.
Impressive, boy.
This is a happy occasion!
You, too, Prince Indra?
Gigi.
Y-Yes?
Give five... no, ten rean to
everyone standing around here.
All hail the Wise Prince!
Yes, Master!
Thank you!
Banzai! Banzai! Banzai!
He is truly the one
acknowledged by the divine!
On an auspicious day,
Here you go!
a time when something good happens,
it is considered the duty
of the nobility to share it
with everyone rather than
keep it all to themselves.
It is said that third-rate
nobles oppose this,
second-rate nobles go along
with it out of sheer pride,
and first-rate nobles just do it as
if it's the natural course of action.
If I may, Wise Prince...
Please allow me to refuse
this aid you have offered.
Why?
Because I wish to become your knight.
To do that, I must
advance on my own merit
and become worthy of
living in your service.
Denied.
Why?
To accept help and then slack
off would be inexcusable,
but only second-rate knights
accept out of sheer pride.
S-Second-rate?
If you want to be first-rate,
do not be ashamed to accept aid.
Just give even more back to your master.
If you want to be worthy of me,
that's what you need to do.
Understood!
Impressive. It only took
one well-spoken line.
He's grown into one intriguing little sprout.
Brilliant, is he not?
That is why I thought...
your granddaughter would
be perfect for him.
Born Blessed, So I'll Obtain Ultimate Power
We are outside the palace.
No need for excessive formalities.
Uncle, stand beside me.
Right.
And now, Leviathan.
Just slight menace.
Only enough to inspire awe and respect.
Good. I don't sense any treachery.
So melodramatic.
I'm surprised he can keep his
cool at such a young age.
He's gotta be the number
one prince, right?
That is why I called him the "Wise."
It's just as fitting as
your "Lightning," no?
I'll be just a thundering old
fart soon enough, though.
Noah will grow into his "Wise" title.
It has been determined that he will make
his first campaign alone, after all.
A solo first campaign?!
Don't they normally take a robust escort?
But with this one, I can believe it.
The people have turned
their attention to me.
This would be an opportune
time to escort His Majesty.
Wait, could it be...
I knew it. Then I'll
gladly accept his favor.
This is what's so amazing about Noah.
I told you all that to create an
opportunity for him to escort me.
He understood that and leapt on board.
Oh? Impressive.
I didn't even notice.
As free-wheeling as you are,
you lack sensitivity.
That's why you and your wife quarrel
endlessly over trivial things.
You got that right!
All the more reason to feel at
ease giving him my granddaughter!
Now, Uncle, we must talk.
So, what'd you wanna talk about?
Well...
Luthier.
I think I will disinherit
the crown prince.
Episode 11
Disinheritance
I had hoped things would work out,
but I've been left with no
choice but to deem him unfit.
Why?
The matter with Gilbert.
I see.
I couldn't let His Majesty
kill his own child,
so I tried to convince him to give
Gilbert no more than a life sentence.
But then the crown prince...
That in itself was not a mistake,
but there must have been some
other way to go about it.
That scared the hell outta me, too.
If he were to become the emperor,
there'd definitely be a major purge.
Yes.
In particular, Henry, Oscar, and Noah
would be the first ones eliminated.
Such pettiness and cruelty...
I cannot allow such a man to succeed me.
That's fine, but what's next?
Who's gonna be the next crown prince?
I haven't decided.
You can't be like that.
You're an old man now.
If you drop dead before you choose
an heir, it'll divide the nation.
His Majesty must have
come to Indra for advice
because no one else could
be so frank with him.
To say I haven't decided is inaccurate.
But if I announce my decision now,
it would only lead to more feuding.
That's still better than leaving
the crown prince's post vacant.
True.
If I may speak, Your Majesty...
What is it?
Perhaps you could tell the public only
that you have prepared your will...
and that the name of your
heir is written in it.
That won't work.
Anyone could forge a
will after he's dead.
Yes, which is why His Majesty would
hide his will inside his body.
A simple example would be a false
tooth with writing engraved in it,
or perhaps some sort of magic...
I get it. If it's on his person at
all times, no one can change it.
Remarkable, Noah! That is a fine idea!
You wait outside, as well.
Let no one enter.
Yes, sire.
Who's he?
Not to worry.
He is a liaison, the sort who is always
present at occasions of this nature.
He cannot hear, speak, or read.
I will take my leave now.
Now, Noah, you've made
an excellent proposal.
I've decided to employ it.
Yes, sire. Also, one other thing...
I think command of our full military
should be returned to you,
including Henry's post as
minister-prince of military affairs
and mine as governor-general
of the first imperial guard.
Good point. If anyone who objects to
his will is in command of any forces,
he could remove all the others
and install himself as emperor.
A sound argument...
but I wouldn't have expected it from
one of the guys who'll lose his post.
Impressive, boy.
He'll make a fine husband
for your granddaughter, no?
He sure will.
An edict expressing gratitude to me while
relieving me of my governor-general post.
And that one will be for Henry.
That was an awfully simplistic order.
I suppose he's been trained
so that he can only carry out
a certain few specific orders.
So how are you gonna handle the
crown prince's disinheritance?
In my opinion as minister-prince
of justice,
that's entirely up to you.
Your Majesty is free to name or
disinherit your heir as you please.
No one can meddle in your decision.
I see.
But unlike Gilbert, Albert has not
committed a specific offense.
For that reason, it may be best to
let him remain a prince, at least.
Then how about this?
"Albert has not committed treason
against me or the empire,
but he is not capable enough for
me to entrust the empire to him.
He will thus be stripped of
his role as crown prince,
but retain the title of prince."
I think that sounds excellent.
Great. So, emperor,
does Albert have any chance
of becoming your heir again?
No.
He really has given up on Albert.
Then you should probably make that clear.
Perhaps you could give him a title?
One like "Ended Prince," for
example, implying that he
cannot advance beyond "prince"?
Oh?
Yes, I like that.
Noah, thank you for your counsel.
Hmm... This won't do...
What's the deal?
That's a lot of mistakes.
And the writing's so convoluted,
no one'll understand it.
What's wrong with you?
I'm taking my son's inheritance away.
Even if this isn't as
grave as taking his life,
I can hardly bear it.
I get it.
Just keep redoing it until you
can write it without hesitation.
Your Majesty, if I may...
Perhaps you should leave what
you've written exactly as it is?
It will remain on the record
as an official edict,
so your feelings will be preserved
in a way that Albert can see them.
And if he can accept that
and continue to push on as a
prince for the empire's sake...
If only you had been...
I will do that. Excellent advice.
Thank you, Your Majesty.
Hold it!
What is it, boy?
This eunuch visibly reacted
after looking at the edict.
What?
And then he hesitated.
Because he knows what it says.
You won't escape!
Cruz!
I-Is something the matter?
That man can read.
Wha—
This is a result of my own negligence!
Please... Please forgive me!
How shall he be punished, Noah?
Execution. To be carried out immediately.
The reason?
He lied about being unable to read
so he could assume what could be
considered a key role in the empire.
He has sullied
Your Majesty's imperial court.
Shouldn't we get some information
out of him before we kill him?
That would tell us who is behind this,
making it possible to
punish them both, but...
What if it was Albert?
Or one of the other princes?
I see.
Yes. Let's not do that.
Thank you for your counsel.
Noah, please continue to serve me
as minister-prince of justice.
Of course.
What shall we do with Cruz?
His only crime is a lack of oversight.
Six months of reduced pay should suffice.
You heard him, Cruz.
See to it, as well.
Y-Yes, Your Majesty!
Thank you so much!
Is it done?
Since the man was a eunuch,
I carried out his punishment personally.
And?
Prince Noah is remarkable.
I almost wonder if he can read minds.
Albert...
What will you do?
I... know not.
Whoever he may be,
even if I can't entrust the empire
to him, he is still my son.
Incidentally, are you familiar
with the name "Leviathan"?
Yes. He was one of the four sages
who lent their powers to the
emperor during the Silver Age.
It seems that Leviathan is
lending his powers to Noah now.
Well, that is splendid!
If anyone can surpass the Silver Age,
perhaps it is Prince Noah!
Yes. He does have the
potential, at least.
I will watch carefully
to see how he grows from here.
At your leave.
Um... Your Highness?
Where are you heading from here?
It's unusual for you to insert
yourself in conversations like this.
I-I'm very sorry!
It's just that you looked
so lost in thought...
It's fine. Your assessment is correct.
Then...
Remain at ease.
We are indeed riding into a challenge,
but our lives are not in danger.
What do you mean?
We're headed to my brother's,
the crown prince's, mansion.
High above in the clear blue sky
The white birds are taking flight
Signaling that a new wind has arrived
Well, this is truly a rare visit.
Singing to the town below
I wasn't expecting the minister-prince
of justice at the peak of his popularity.
In the heat of the busy city street
And the roaring voices of the crowd
I have come for an audience with
Your Highness the Crown Prince.
Everything that we have
waited for is here
The door to a new age opens wide
Please forgive me for
visiting without notice.
You're always so formal.
Well, I suppose that's why you're
the minister-prince of justice.
Holding on to just a single wish inside
Anyway, relax.
Here, we're just two brothers.
Counting all the freezing
nights I have survived
Thank you.
Stand by outside the mansion.
Understood.
Having my guard wait outside is a show
of my trust in the crown prince.
I'm sure Shirley understands that now.
Would you prefer the
living room or the garden?
I've heard that your garden is kept
by the renowned gardener, Torrant.
I've been hoping for a chance to see it.
Oh, yes, I never showed it to you, did I?
Very good. Right this way, then.
It's beautiful.
You can tell?
Yes. That tree with the
double trunks, for example.
I've never seen one so magnificent.
Your eyes are as keen as ever.
That was a gift from a member of my
household that I sent away to work.
It cost 50,000 rean, apparently.
I can believe that.
I'll have it sent to your mansion later.
You saw its quality with one look.
The tree itself would be happier
with a man who understands it.
Then I will gratefully accept it.
This will be the second time I've
personally given you something.
You seem to have mastered
that magic sword, no?
I only gave it to you as a little joke,
but that has taught me
that great power only belongs in
the hands of the right people.
Summer is upon us again.
Hm? Yes.
I asked earlier,
and His Majesty said he will travel north
to escape the heat again this year.
What differs from previous years
is that he intends to take
you with him this year.
In recent years,
when the emperor left the
capital to escape the heat,
he had the crown prince
rule in his stead.
This allowed him to gradually give the
crown prince more government duties
as a rehearsal for his
future reign as emperor.
But doing away with that means...
How much...
do you know?
His Majesty only gave me
a roundabout explanation.
He said he wanted to give you a thorough
education on the essence of ruling.
I beg your pardon?
He is the kind of great ruler
we see only once a millennia.
I imagine he has come up with many
methods that we could never even imagine.
I can only guess that he wants
to teach them to you now.
His Majesty does intend
to take Albert with him,
but probably only because keeping him
close means one less thing to worry about.
Even so,
if spending time together
helps my brother understand
His Majesty's feelings...
I see. Thank you, Noah.
Your Highness.
Alichey.
I'm up next, so I came to greet you.
Of course.
What is it?
Nothing. I will sing
with all I have in me,
just like you told me to.
Good.
Sweetly echoing my mother's lullaby
Orange fire casting shadows on the wall
Feigning sleep I held on
tight to father's back
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Becky Cottrill
Edgar Cruz
Gabriella Alabanza
S Bilyeu
Safe in his arms
You must be strong
To protect the weak
I know this truth well
Because he taught me so
Crying in frustration
My tears become a river now
Carrying hope to tomorrow
Enter.
Pardon me, Master.
I'm sorry to visit so late at night.
There is a woman here
who wishes to see you.
Her name?
Olivia Coil.
I don't know that name.
But if she wasn't someone important,
Zoey would have sent her away.
Fine. Let her in.
You said your name is Olivia?
There is nothing we can
take when we depart
What is your business
here at this hour?
I bring you a tip.
The crown prince, Second Prince Albert,
Blooming in the glory
plans to lead
a coup tonight...
For the future I had always dreamed of
I will stand right here
and force His Majesty
to abdicate the throne.
Singing out a song of blessing